(Howard:)Glad to hear it.
(Sheldon:)I'll be able to return
to work tomorrow.
(Raj:)Yay.
(Sheldon:)Well, why isn't
everyone happy?
(Sheldon:)Your little ray of sunshine
is ready to beam again.
(Penny:)You really don't know why?
No.
But I knew that his “yay”
was sarcastic.
(Sheldon:)Not bad for a guy
whose last bowel movement
(Sheldon:)sounded like rain on a roof.
(Leonard:)Let me refresh your memory.
(Sheldon:)Penny,
(Sheldon:)rub Vicks on my chest.
(Penny:)Sheldon, I cooked you breakfast.
(Penny:)I made your bed.
(Penny:)I checked your mouth for thrush.
(Penny:)You can rub your own chest.
(Sheldon:)Oh, sure, grope every other
male on the planet,
(Sheldon:)but draw the line with me.
(Bernadette:)I brought you a little
care package from work.
(Bernadette:)It's our latest
antiviral
(Bernadette:)and the best decongestant
we make.
(Sheldon:)I hope laughter
is the best medicine,
(Sheldon:)'cause this care package
is a joke.